http://www.vfcu.org/privacypolicy

Our
West Lawn, Shillington and Exeter branches will be open from 10:00 AM - 3:00 PM on Friday 12/11.PersonalLOANSAuto LoansCredit CardsDebt ProtectionHome Equity LoansHome Equity Lines of CreditHome ImprovementMortgagesPersonal Loans/Lines of CreditRV/Boat LoansShare Secured LoansSkip-A-PaymentStudent LoansACCOUNTSCheckingHSAIRASavingsShare CertificatesLucky SaversMoney MarketYouthSERVICESMobile BankingDigital BankingMobile PaymentsLoan Payment OptionsClickSWITCHDefensive DrivingInsuranceFinSavvyForeign CurrencyMedicareWire TransfersFINANCIAL PLANNINGDiscount BrokerageGuided Wealth PortfolioInvestment ServicesTrust and Estate ServicesBusinessACCOUNTSOverviewCheckingResources & FAQsLOANSCredit CardsLoansApplicationSERVICESCommercial InsuranceCorporate Retirement PlanningDigital BankingMerchant ProcessingNight DepositsSpecial ServicesServices for Other Credit UnionsResourcesEDUCATIONFinancial EducationCredit ReportRequest a
Community EducatorPROGRAMSEmbarkNewlyweds/Wedding LoansScholarshipVeteransVisions Loves EducatorsRATES and CALCULATORSRatesCalculatorsARTICLES and MAGAZINEArticlesMoneyMatters Financial MagazineADDITIONAL INFORMATIONFormsDisclosuresShared BranchingAbout UsAbout UsBecome a MemberBecome a VolunteerLocationsContact UsVisions CaresCareersNewsSecurityEventsAdvocacyPrivacy PolicyFeedbacki-general Privacy Notice FACTSWHAT DOES Visions Federal Credit Union
DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?Rev. 01/2019Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.What?The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:Social Security number and incomeAccount balances and payment historyCredit history and credit scoresHow?All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’ personal information; the reasons Visions Federal Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.Reasons we can share your personal informationDoes Visions Federal Credit Union Share?Can you limit this sharing?For our everyday business purposes-
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus YesNoFor our marketing purposes-
to offer our products and services to youYesNoFor joint marketing with other financial companiesYesNoFor our affiliates’ everyday business purposes-
information about your transactions and experiencesYesYesFor our affiliates’ everyday business purposes-
information about your creditworthiness NoWe don't shareFor our affiliates to market to youYesYesFor non-affiliates to market to youNoWe don't shareTo Limit Our SharingCall 800.242.2120 – Option 4Visit one of our branchesPlease note:If you are a new member, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.Questions?Call 800.242.2120 or visit one of our branches.Who we areWho is providing this notice?Visions Federal Credit Union; Visions Analysis LLC and Visions Insurance Agency LLCWhat we doHow does Visions FCU
protect my personal information?We use security measures that comply with federal law to protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.How does Visions FCU collect my personal information?We collect your personal information when you
Open an account or apply for a loanApply for a loanUse your credit or debit cardMake a deposit or withdrawal from your accountShow current Government ID
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.Why can't I limit all sharing?Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes- such as information about
your creditworthinessaffiliates from using your information to market to yousharing for non-affiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.DefinitionsAffiliatesCompanies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
Visions Federal Credit Union affiliates include: Visions Analysis LLC and Visions Insurance Agency LLC.Non-affiliatesCompanies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
Visions Federal Credit Union does not share with non-affiliates.Joint MarketingA formal agreement between non-affiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
Our joint marketing partners include financial service provider, non-financial companies, and others.Other important informationVisions will update its privacy policy from time to time. Please see https://www.visionsfcu.org/PrivacyPolicy/ for the most current version.Refer A FriendGet rewarded for sharing Visions with your friends and family.Get $25 when they open an account!Refer Now
You are leaving the Visions Federal Credit Union web site. The privacy and security policies of the external link may differ from Visions Federal Credit Union.
Visions Federal Credit Union does not own or control external links and is not responsible for the availability or accuracy of their content.
ContinueCancelLog in here with your Online Banking ID:Online EnrollmentForgot Password
